(Bernadette:)Can I get your opinion on something
that happened at work today?
(Penny:)-Yeah, sure.
-of course.
(Bernadette:)I did something that will either
make me look like a lovable goof
(Bernadette:)or a horrible monster damned
to spend eternity in hell.
(Amy:)I'm sure it's lovable.
(Penny:)I'm gonna go with monster.
What do you got?
(Bernadette:)Well, there's this lady
in our office who's retiring,
(Bernadette:)and they were passing around one of
those big cards for us to sign...
(Bernadette:)Okay.
(Bernadette:)No one told me she was in a horrible
car accident over the weekend
(Bernadette:)and what I was signing
was not a retirement card
but was actually a "get well" card.
(Penny:)I'm liking my odds here.
(Bernadette:)So on the card, in the hospital,
(Bernadette:)next to the woman who's clinging
to life are the words,
"Hey, Vivian. You deserve this.
(Bernadette:)And at least with you gone,
no one will steal my yogurt
out of the fridge."
No!
"LOL. Smiley face."
(Amy:)Oh, my gosh.